<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Logs</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/https-logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/https-logs/</guid>
      <description>HTTP Logs Clicking on &amp;ldquo;HTTP Logs&amp;rdquo; in the left navigation bar opens up a view of Kibana. Kibana will allow you to search through your logs to dig deeper into trends you found in Graphite or Grafana. To open Kibana in its own window, click the “open in new window” button at the top of the Kibana frame.
On the Discover view in Kibana, you can either select items from the left nav, or type searches into the search bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better than a CDN</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/better-than-a-cdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/better-than-a-cdn/</guid>
      <description>The Section platform provides superior application performance, availability, scalability, and security by putting architects, developers, and sysadmins in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat.
Unlike legacy CDN&amp;rsquo;s, Section has designed an Application Edge system for modern agile development.
Section differs from contemporary CDN platforms by:
 allowing a choice of reverse proxy technology. allowing engineers to use normal tooling to configure the system. providing a real time devops toolset.  Unlike with legacy CDNs, with Section:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agency Ready</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/agency-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/agency-ready/</guid>
      <description>Section is built to streamline the process of managing groups of websites.
If you work at an agency, you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with the unique challenges that come with overseeing large groups of sites. You want to be able to:
 log in with one user account for yourself and see all your client sites. give separate logins to individual clients so that they can see only their data and not that of your other clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Network</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/global-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/global-network/</guid>
      <description>The Section platform runs a high availability Global Network so that your Application Edge is ready when and where your customers need it.
Section forms its Global Network by combining the network, compute and security features of the most popular cloud services such as:
 Amazon AWS Google Compute Engine Microsoft Azure DigitalOcean Packet Rackcorp  Our reach continues to grow as Section incorporates more cloud providers into its Global Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxy Options</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/proxy-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/proxy-options/</guid>
      <description>Unlike Legacy CDNs which generally are fixed on a single proxy, Section allows you to choose the proxies that suit your application architecture.
Depending on your needs, you can run a single module or combine multiple modules for enhanced performance benefit:
 Performance: Varnish Cache (versions 3, 4, 5, 6). Google&amp;rsquo;s PageSpeed. Nginx, and Nginx+Lua. Scalability: Varnish Cache . Nginx. Availability: Varnish Cache . Nginx+Lua. Security: ModSecurity. ThreatX. Signal Sciences.  These are just some of the reverse proxies that are available to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Ready</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/developer-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/developer-ready/</guid>
      <description>For too long, CDNs have remained in the dark ages of waterfall processes with no integration into the agile development lifecycle. Agile methods just aren&amp;rsquo;t something that CDNs understand.
As application logic moves to the edge, Section brings the tools and processes you need to build an ideal, flexible architecture.
By allowing any engineer in your team to run a Developer PoP, you can bring the Application Edge right down onto your laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Ready</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/devops-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/devops-ready/</guid>
      <description>Whether a website is yours or your client&amp;rsquo;s, you need to have the right information available to you immediately when you&amp;rsquo;re running a mission critical application.
Section runs a detailed, real-time logging and metrics platform to provide you with the vital diagnostics.
DevOps teams need a few things to get their job done well:
 Continual improvement: Section collects hundreds of metrics about how your HTTP traffic is performing and provides long term retenion out of the box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNS Options</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/dns-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/dns-options/</guid>
      <description>Section uses DNS to route requests to the most appropriate datacenter.
When you sign up for Section, you configure a CNAME record to point your traffic to our Application Edge, just like a legacy CDN.
Section also includes a global anycast DNS network with all plans. This can be useful if you run your site as a bare domain.
Whilst you can choose to move your DNS to our nameservers, that&amp;rsquo;s completely optional at all plan levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTPS Options</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/https-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/https-options/</guid>
      <description>All Section plans include a complete HTTPS solution.
On our platform you can:
 Take advantage of our free SSL certificates that are automatically configured and renewed. Upload your own Standard, Wildcard, or Extended Validation certificate  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aperture Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/section/monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Each Section environment has its own overview page. The overview page displays general information about the environment&amp;rsquo;s module stack and HTTP request flow, any recent errors between Section and the origin server, and a number of links to more detailed information about the environment such as DNS information and HTTP logs.
Module Stack All module stack configurations running on Section begin with the edge module (the very first module that incoming HTTP requests hit when they enter Section) and ends with the LastProxy (the last module that incoming HTTP requests pass through before leaving Section and hitting your origin server).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
