<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developer Workflow on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developer Workflow on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Set-up Section Developer PoP</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/setting-up-your-developer-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/setting-up-your-developer-pop/</guid>
      <description>Section Developer PoP runs on Kubernetes. Minikube is a miniature, prepackaged Kubernetes cluster that works locally on a desktop Microsoft Windows, Mac or Linux computer.
Minikube runs in the free and open source VirtualBox.
 Verify that you have installed VirtualBox Download and install Minikube v1.6.2. Version 1.6.2 is the Section supported version of Minikube. https://github.com/kubernetes/minikube/releases/tag/v1.6.2 Download and install kubectl v1.16.2. Version v1.16.2 is the Section supported version of kubectl. https://kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Load Setup Into Developer PoP</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/loading-your-setup-into-the-developer-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/loading-your-setup-into-the-developer-pop/</guid>
      <description>1. Clone application&amp;rsquo;s git repository Clone your application&amp;rsquo;s git repository located in the Advanced Config menu in the Section portal.
  URL from GIT repo   Clone with git clone &amp;lt;url-from-advanced-config&amp;gt;
2. Add the Dev PoP remote to your repository  Open the Dev Pop UI: minikube service -n section-shared developer-pop    Section app ready to connect to Aperture   Connect Aperture   Connect to Aperture button   Grant Access  The application section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop with the Developer PoP</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/developing-with-the-developer-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/developer-workflow/developing-with-the-developer-pop/</guid>
      <description>1. Locally Override DNS to point at the Developer PoP You will need to modify your local host file and point the Hosted Name(s) for your service at the IP address given by the command minikube ip.
192.168.99.100 www.example.com This will override the DNS endpoint for that domain and force traffic through the Dev PoP and then to your origin address.
Your origin could be your production webserver, production load balancer, development webserver — whatever you configured for in the Dev PoP UI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
