<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modules on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modules on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Hash</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/consistent-hash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/consistent-hash/</guid>
      <description>What does it do This module is built on the Section OpenResty module and provides a more robust upstream definition by load balancing traffic using an internal consistent hash to select the right upstream node.
Available hashed key values:
 True-Client-IP URI Path  See the set up guide to implement this module into your module stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSP Report</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/csp-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/csp-report/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Automatically detect and mitigate certain types of attacks, including Cross Site Scripting (XSS) and data injection.
From https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/CSP
 A primary goal of CSP is to mitigate and report XSS attacks. XSS attacks exploit the browser&amp;rsquo;s trust of the content received from the server. Malicious scripts are executed by the victim&amp;rsquo;s browser because the browser trusts the source of the content, even when it&amp;rsquo;s not coming from where it seems to be coming from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ModSecurity</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/modsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/modsecurity/</guid>
      <description>Modsecurity Configuration The initial configuration in a repository starts ModSecurity’s SecRuleEngine in DetectionOnly mode (this writes log entries but never executes any disruptive actions) with rules from base_rules &amp;amp; optional_rules. This is a great starting point, as you can immediately see possible threats without stopping legitimate traffic to your site.
Note: Whilst many tutorials and guides use Symbolic Links to have content appear in the rules/activated_rules directory, symbolic links complicate the use of source control &amp;amp; local development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenResty</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/openresty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/openresty/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Use the power of Lua to achieve edge side rewrites and much more.
Install and configure Nginx/Lua on a globally distributed Edge Compute Platform with the confidence of DevOps control.
Section takes the complications out of installing and configuring the software by providing you with:
 A fully managed instance of the most up-to-date version. Git-backed workflows for easy version control. A development environment to test your configurations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radware Bot Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/radware-bot-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/radware-bot-manager/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Secure your application from automated threats with Radware Bot Manager
Radware Bot Manager specializes in non-human traffic detection and management. Their best-of-breed bot management solution secures online businesses against automated threats such as content and price scraping, account takeover, gift card fraud, skewed analytics, ad fraud, and application DoS.
Radware’s Bot Manager bot detection engine utilizes multiple techniques to identify bots including proprietary Intent-based Deep Behavior Analysis (IDBA), user behavior analysis, device and browser fingerprinting, IP reputation, and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signal Sciences</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/signal-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/signal-sciences/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Providing real-time protection for any application, against any attack, with integrations into any DevOps toolchain.
Signal Sciences was created by CISOs, CTOs, and engineers looking to integrate advanced website security with cloud solutions and DevOps workflows. Signal Sciences analyzes and blocks threats in real-time, with 95% of customers using it in blocking mode, reducing false positives while identifying more threats than other solutions.
Signal Sciences uses contextual information and next-generation cloud analysis to immediately block threats while sending detailed insights to an intuitive dashboard so your development and operations teams can work together to continually improve your web application’s security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SiteSpect</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/sitespect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/sitespect/</guid>
      <description>What does it do SiteSpect provides the world’s only tag-free web and mobile site optimization platform, enabling online businesses to test everything and target anyone.
SiteSpect gives you the power to test your ideas, discover insights, and personalize the entire customer journey. Optimize the user experience without the limitations of JavaScript tags. Typical customers see 10% RPV Lift, 10% Conversion Lift, and a 10X Revenue Benefit.
The world’s leading digital companies rely on SiteSpect to help them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThreatX</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/threat-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/threat-x/</guid>
      <description>What does it do ThreatX is a reverse proxy that inspects and adapts to web site attacks that can infiltrate your web site and cause problems for your business.
Because ThreatX doesn&amp;rsquo;t simply rely upon statically defined rule sets like old WAFs (and CDNs based on those old WAFs) you can expect a higher degree of security.
This also means that there&amp;rsquo;s a lower cost to maintain that level of security, because the adaptive nature of the platform means that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to spend time and money on in-house security experts to keep your rules up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Varnish Cache</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/varnish-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/varnish-cache/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Section implements a pure and unchanged version of the Varnish Cache.
At every opportunity, the implementation of Varnish Cache on the Section platform has been designed to be as close as possible to how it would be if you had installed Varnish Cache yourself locally.
Section uses the official Varnish Cache distributions published by Varnish Cache. Section does not use custom-compiled builds of Varnish Cache.
Varnish Cache is started, listening on port 80.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Waiting Room</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/virtual-waiting-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/virtual-waiting-room/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Maintain control of user experience on your website even during periods of extreme traffic.
Don’t let excess traffic volumes destroy every user’s experience When an unexpected peak traffic event occurs on your website, Section’s Edge Compute Platform can route a nominated portion of users to a Virtual Waiting Room where they can remain while other users successfully navigate, engage with and transact with your website.
Optimal User Experience By placing excess users into the Virtual Waiting Room, the users who are on your website can continue to navigate, search, engage and transact with your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudinary</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/cloudinary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/cloudinary/</guid>
      <description>What does it do Image optimisation module that will compress, resize, crop, transform images to suit the customer&amp;rsquo;s use case. Use Cloudinary to deliver the optimal image for every image viewing context.
Deploying on-the-fly image manipulation and optimization for your website is super simple on Section. Deploy Cloudinary on Section to access all the benefits of the Cloudinary Image Optimization suite:
 High-performance image optimization Crop, scale, transcode, enhance images on the fly Dynamic scaling and cropping of responsive images Device recognition and image manipulation to suit  Deliver faster page loads Image optimization for web is one of the most important elements of delivering faster pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node.js</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/explanations/modules/nodejs/</guid>
      <description>What does it do As an asynchronous event-driven JavaScript runtime, Node.js is designed to build scalable network applications. In Node.js, many connections can be handled concurrently. Upon each connection, the callback is fired, but if there is no work to be done, Node.js will sleep.
HTTP is a first-class citizen in Node.js, designed with streaming and low latency in mind. This makes Node.js well-suited for the foundation of a web library or framework.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
