<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Management on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Management on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add a user to your account</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/add-a-user-to-your-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/add-a-user-to-your-account/</guid>
      <description>Invite a New User via email To invite a new user to your account:
  Invite a New User via email    Click on Account and then Manage Users in the top right of the management console. Enter the user details of the person you want to invite, and click Invite User.  The invited user will receive an email inviting them to join Section and have immediate access to your account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billing Portal</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/billing-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/billing-portal/</guid>
      <description>Once you have set up your account, you will have access to your billing portal within the Account dashboard. The Billing Portal is where you can update your card, view your invoices or cancel your account — all from one convenient interface.
To navigate to the Billing Portal, first click on the &amp;ldquo;gear&amp;rdquo; icon in your menu then navigate to &amp;ldquo;Account&amp;rdquo;. Here you will find the &amp;ldquo;Visit Billing Portal&amp;rdquo; button which will take you to our hosted billing portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Two Factor Authentication on Your Account</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/enable-two-factor-authentication-on-your-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/enable-two-factor-authentication-on-your-account/</guid>
      <description>In addition to a strong password, your account can be further protected by enabling Two Factor Authentication.
To enable two factor authentication:
 Click on the user icon in the top right corner of the management console and click Profile.  If you want to use SMS verification: Ensure your phone number is correct Turn on two factor authentication and choose Receive an SMS on each login  If you want to use an authenticator app, like Google Authenticator or LastPass Authenticator: Turn on two factor authentication and choose Store my code on a device  Finally, for both options, click Save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove a user from your account</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/remove-a-user/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/application-edge-management/user-management/remove-a-user/</guid>
      <description>Remove a User from an Account To remove a user from your account (requires admin status):
 Click on Account and then Manage Users in the top right of the management console. Click Remove From Account next to the relevant user.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
