<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monitoring on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monitoring on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extract domain based metrics</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/extract-domain-based-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/extract-domain-based-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Extract domain based metrics In addition to standard platform metrics you can enable domain based metrics extraction.
Email support@section.io to have this enabled on your account.
Once enabled this will allow you to connect to a metrics endpoint to extract data. (Interesting fact: The endpoint is a prometheus source, you could federate this and point your own prometheus infrastructure at this location)
Data available This endpoint provides the following data: HTTP Requests and Bytes used by Account HTTP Requests and Bytes used by Application HTTP Requests and Bytes used by Environment HTTP Requests and Bytes used by Module (Not normally needed)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a Custom Grafana Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/make-grafana-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/monitoring/make-grafana-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Grafana - Custom Dashboards It may be helpful for you to create a custom dashboard that is specific to your application. You can create your own dashboard by either starting from scratch or duplicating an existing dashboard.
Creating a dashboard from scratch To create a dashboard from scratch:
 Click on the Grafana logo in the left hand corner. Open the Dashboards dropdown. Click on New. Select the type of panel you want to display (Graph, singlestat, table, pie chart, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
