<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Going Live on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Going Live on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating an application</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/create-application-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/create-application-edge/</guid>
      <description>On your main account dashboard, click Create application.  Enter the name of your live web site. Do not include the protocol (i.e. http or https). The system will try to automatically determine the IP of your origin. Click Next.  Click Performance, then click Varnish Cache v5.2 Basic. Click Next.  Enter an account name. Think of this as the organization/company that your website belongs to. (click here a more in-depth explanation of an account).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up DNS</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/set-up-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/set-up-dns/</guid>
      <description>To get your users to connect to Section servers you need to make updates to DNS.
This DNS change will point the traffic to Section servers.
This tutorial works with a domain name that contains a prefix, like the www. prefix in www.section.io.
If you are working with a site that doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a prefix please look at bare domain support with Section.
 Set up the CNAME record  In the management console, click DNS in the left hand menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Automatic SSL</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/enable-automatic-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/going-live/enable-automatic-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Turning on automatic HTTPS  In the management console, click HTTPS in the left hand menu.  Click Renew Certificate. You&amp;rsquo;ll get a message saying that your certificates have been set up.   Congratulations! You are now live with Section.
If you have any trouble, consider looking at our HTTPS Troubleshooting guides.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
