<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Performance Optimization on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Performance Optimization on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review Your Metrics</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/review-your-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/review-your-metrics/</guid>
      <description>WHY: To understand how to improve your site, you first need a benchmark for where you are now.
HOW: After you go live, wait about an hour for data to populate. While Section’s real time reporting will show data inside the first minute of go live, you should wait an hour for trends to emerge. Then use the evaluation guide above to look at your key metrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup your Local Environment</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/setup-your-local-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/setup-your-local-environment/</guid>
      <description>WHY: Before you make any changes to your cache configuration, we recommend you test them locally first. In order to test, you need to setup your local environment.
HOW: To test configuration changes locally, visit our Developer PoP tutorial. Many customers also choose to integrate a staging site with the Section platform as a part of their developer workflow. If you do not want to do this step, you can skip it and make your changes live on production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize your Configuration</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/optimize-your-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/optimize-your-configuration/</guid>
      <description>WHY: Based on your metrics evaluation, you should have identified areas you want to improve. These changes will help you get the most out of Section
HOW: To optimize your configuration, please visit our modules page and browse our guides on the modules in your stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track your Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/track-your-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/track-your-changes/</guid>
      <description>WHY: Everytime you change your configuration, Section will log that history. This allows you to see what was changed and then review metrics to see how your site performed before and after the change.
HOW: In the repository tab under commits you will see a list of the commits that have been made to your application. You can see what that looks like for Bootcamp here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Website</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/monitor-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/tutorials/performance-optimization/monitor-your-website/</guid>
      <description>WHY: You may not want to be checking your metrics everyday, but you want to know if something is wrong so you can fix it. With Alerts you can set benchmarks for your metrics and be alerted via your preferred notification system.
HOW: Under the alerting tab you can identify a metric using graphite query string and at what value you want to be alerted. More details here.
For more in-depth guides on evaluating your website&amp;rsquo;s performance and activity, see our debugging and monitoring guides.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
