<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Performance Evaluation on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Performance Evaluation on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cache Effectiveness</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/understand-if-your-varnish-cache-is-effective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/understand-if-your-varnish-cache-is-effective/</guid>
      <description>Whenever a request reaches a Varnish Cache instance, one of four outcomes occurs: hit, miss, pass, or synth.
A key metric when evaluating website performance is cache hit rate. Cache hit rate is a measure of how effectively the cache is responding to customer requests.
A hit means that the cache responded to the request with a cached resource.
A miss means that the cache tried to respond to the request with a cached resource but could not do so because it did not have a copy of the requested resource in its memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover your quick Cache Wins</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/discover-your-quick-cache-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/discover-your-quick-cache-wins/</guid>
      <description>Your website has several different types of content that can be cached: HTML, Images, CSS, and JS are the main file types for consideration.
 HTML is the set of instructions required to load the page. Images are any images or icons you load. CSS is the style instruction for how to load images, text, and content on the page. JS is small scripts your browser will run when it is instructed to by the HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncover how often you are using HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/uncover-how-often-you-are-using-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/uncover-how-often-you-are-using-https/</guid>
      <description>What is HTTP(S)? HTTP is a protocol for how web requests are handled. HTTPS is an enhanced version of that protocol to add security by encrypting your customers data so it is protected from threats. You can see when a webpage has HTTPS because the url will show a green padlock.
Why is it important? The percentage of requests that have HTTPS show how often your customer data is protected. If this ratio is low, you are putting your customers’ data at a higher risk for incident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up Real User Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/performance/rum/</guid>
      <description>Section offers free real user monitoring for any customer that signs up and begins their trial. This enables you to see how your own visitors are experiencing your website performance with the use of a simple JavaScript snippet. Data includes:
 Back end, front end, and full page load time Throughput Traffic by user agent (browser, device type)  Setting up RUM in Section To add RUM to your website, simply login to your Section account and go to &amp;ldquo;Real User Monitoring&amp;rdquo; under &amp;ldquo;Set Up&amp;rdquo; in the left navigation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
