<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Set up Virtual Waiting Room on Section</title>
    <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Set up Virtual Waiting Room on Section</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021 Section.</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Acquire GoSquared Credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/go-squared-credentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/go-squared-credentials/</guid>
      <description>GoSquared Credentials File gosquared-visitor-count
You need to add a file to the root of the repository called: gosquared-visitor-count
The content of file should be: &amp;lt;threshold&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;secret&amp;gt; varnish &amp;lt;hostname&amp;gt; &amp;lt;api_key&amp;gt;
 Where “threshold” is the max number of customer you want on your site. Where “ID” comes from end of URL when you are logged into gosquared. Where “secret” is a string with no spaces that only you know. Where &amp;ldquo;hostname&amp;rdquo; is the first hostname(domain name) used in your Section Application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control User Threshold</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/control-user-threshold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/control-user-threshold/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Virtual Waiting Room module offers an easy to use interface to control the max number of concurrent users on the site.
Increase/Decrease user threshold The maximum number of concurrent users can be increased/decreased easily by using the counter under the Control Visitor Count section.
  This can also be controlled directly by changing the threshold value in the Advanced Configuration and the GoSquared Credentials file
The default behavior is to force all users to be rechecked if you reduce the number of users allowed on your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design the Waiting Room</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/edit-waiting-room-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/edit-waiting-room-html/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Virtual Waiting Room module offers a convinient way to design your waiting room page.
Edit the Virtual Waiting Room HTML The HTML to be displayed when the users are put in a queue can be edited under the Upload HTML section.
  A preview of the page after it has been uploaded is provided under the Preview HTML tab.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toggle Virtual Waiting Room Module</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/toggle-virtual-waiting-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/toggle-virtual-waiting-room/</guid>
      <description>Overview The modular nature of the Section platform allows you to easily turn the module on or off. When in a disabled state the module acts as a reverse proxy.
Toggle Virtual Waiting Room The Virtual Waiting Room can easily be turned on and off using the toggle provided under the Control Visitor Count section.
  This can also be controlled directly from the Advanced Configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Virtual Waiting Room Advanced Configuration</title>
      <link>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/virtual-waiting-room-advanced-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.section.io/docs/how-tos/module-integrations/virtual-waiting-room/virtual-waiting-room-advanced-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Waiting Module Settings Once your application has been set up with Virtual Waiting Room you will find the following files under Advanced Config &amp;gt; virtualwaitingroom in the Aperture portal.
virtualwaitingroom.json virtualwaitingroom.json will contain the configuration of your virtual waiting room and should have the following data.
 The settings are as follows :
 &amp;quot;api_key&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;&amp;lt;YourGoSquaredAPIKey&amp;gt;&amp;quot;  This will be provided by the Sectin support team.
 &amp;quot;threshold&amp;quot; : 1000  Threshold is the max number of concurrent customers you want on your site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
